https://www.beltile.com/privacy-policy/

Special Offer
Sign Up for exclusive updates, new arrivals and insider-only discounts
Subscribe to our Newsletter
Updates, discounts, some special offers and more.
Submit
Hours 10 AM - 4 PM Eastern
866-925-TILE (8453)
100% GUARANTEED SECURE SHOPPING
sales@beltile.com
Shipping USA & Canada
If you don't see it, Ask!
Fast Delivery
Live Customer Support (Mon-Fri)
Fast Delivery
Live Customer Support (Mon-Fri)
Sale Wholesale
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how BelTile uses and protects any information that you give BelTile when you use this website. BelTile is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. BelTile may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
Name
Contact information including email address
Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
For the exhaustive list of cookies we collect see the List of cookies we collect section.
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website.
Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
CCPA Privacy Rights (Do Not Sell My Personal Information)
Under the CCPA, among other rights, California consumers have the right to:
Request that a business that collects a consumer's personal data disclose the categories and specific pieces of personal data that a business has collected about consumers.
Request that a business delete any personal data about the consumer that a business has collected.
Request that a business that sells a consumer's personal data, not sell the consumer's personal data.
If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.
Google DoubleClick DART Cookie
Google is one of a third-party vendor on our site. It also uses cookies, known as DART cookies, to serve ads to our site visitors based upon their visit to www.website.com and other sites on the internet. However, visitors may choose to decline the use of DART cookies by visiting the Google ad and content network Privacy Policy at the following URL – https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads
Advertising Partners Privacy Policies
You may consult this list to find the Privacy Policy for each of the advertising partners of Beltile.
Third-party ad servers or ad networks uses technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on Beltile, which are sent directly to users' browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.
Note that Beltile has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.
Third Party Privacy Policies
Beltile's Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options.
You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options. To know more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, it can be found at the browsers' respective websites.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at sales@beltile.com
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to .
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
List of cookies we collect
The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.
COOKIE nameCOOKIE Description
CART
The association with your shopping cart.
CATEGORY_INFO
Stores the category info on the page, that allows to display pages more quickly.
COMPARE
The items that you have in the Compare Products list.
CURRENCY
Your preferred currency
CUSTOMER
An encrypted version of your customer id with the store.
CUSTOMER_AUTH
An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.
CUSTOMER_INFO
An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.
CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS
Stores the Customer Segment ID
EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE
A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.
FRONTEND
You sesssion ID on the server.
GUEST-VIEW
Allows guests to edit their orders.
LAST_CATEGORY
The last category you visited.
LAST_PRODUCT
The most recent product you have viewed.
NEWMESSAGE
Indicates whether a new message has been received.
NO_CACHE
Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART
A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.
POLL
The ID of any polls you have recently voted in.
POLLN
Information on what polls you have voted on.
RECENTLYCOMPARED
The items that you have recently compared.
STF
Information on products you have emailed to friends.
STORE
The store view or language you have selected.
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE
Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS
The products that you have recently viewed.
WISHLIST
An encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.
WISHLIST_CNT
The number of items in your Wishlist.
Ceramic Tiles Ceramic TilesBack Ceramic Tiles Subway Tile Subway TileBack Subway Tile Metro Rectified Subway Tile Elongated Tile Royal Crackle Beltile Vogue Wavy Beveled Subway Tiles Beveled Subway TilesBack Beveled Subway Tiles Metro Retro 4x8 Parisian Modern Arctic Ceramic Tile Trims Ceramic Tile TrimsBack Ceramic Tile Trims Metro Trims Vogue Wavy Trims Royal Crackle Trims Arctic White Trims Wall Tiles Wall TilesBack Wall Tiles Metro
Collections
Classic 4 1/4 x 4 1/4 and 6x6 Tiles
Crackle Tiles
Sale
30-Day Returns
Fast Delivery
Live Customer Support (Mon-Fri)
Handpainted Tiles Handpainted TilesBack Handpainted Tiles Crackle Tiles Crackle TilesBack Crackle Tiles Tunisian Crackle Royal Crackle Tunisian Tiles Tunisian TilesBack Tunisian Tiles Iznik Tiles Murals Patterned Field Tiles Tunisian Trims Borders Antique Replicas Solid Field Tiles Italian Tiles Italian TilesBack Italian Tiles Ceramic Patterns Ceramic Borders Ceramic Solids Decorative Floor Tiles Lavastone Patterns Lavastone Solids Murals Moroccan Tiles Moroccan TilesBack Moroccan Tiles Andalusian Tile Zellige Tiles Blue and White
Japanese Tiles
Collections
View All Handpainted
Blue and White Tiles
Sale
30-Day Returns
Fast Delivery
Live Customer Support (Mon-Fri)
Porcelain Tiles Porcelain TilesBack Porcelain Tiles Glazed Porcelain Mosaics Glazed Porcelain MosaicsBack Glazed Porcelain Mosaics Hexagon Porcelain Mosaic Penny Round Mosaics Stacked Line Mosaics Arabesque and Lanterns Octagon and Dot Mosaic
Square and Brick Mosaics Glazed Herringbone Pinwheel Spiral Mosaics Basketweave Mosaics 3D Mosaics Unglazed Mosaics Unglazed MosaicsBack Unglazed Mosaics Hexagons Squares Pinwheel / Spiral Rectangles Floor and Wall Tiles Floor and Wall TilesBack Floor and Wall Tiles Wood-Look Planks Limestone Replica Floor Tiles Brick Look Porcelain Hexagon Marble Replica Tiles Cement Replica Industrial Glazed Ceramic Look Wall Only Tiles Wall Only TilesBack Wall Only Tiles Subway Tiles Brick Look
Collections
View All Porcelain
Floor Tiles
Stone Look Tiles
Wood Look Tiles
Sale
30-Day Returns
Fast Delivery
Live Customer Support (Mon-Fri)
Stone Tiles Stone TilesBack Stone Tiles Limestone Tiles Limestone TilesBack Limestone Tiles French Limestone Jerusalem Limestone Portuguese Limestone Octagon with Cabochon Tunisian Limestone Marble Tiles Marble TilesBack Marble Tiles Ming Green Calacatta Carrara Thassos Blue Celeste Onyx Tiles Onyx TilesBack Onyx Tiles Honey Onyx Stone Mosaic Tiles Stone Mosaic TilesBack Stone Mosaic Tiles Basketweave
Octagon and Dot
Pennyround Hexagon Herringbone Brick Mosaic Carpets Waterjet Special Order Mosaics Travertine Tiles Stone Trims and Moldings
Live Customer Support (Mon-Fri)
Glass GlassBack Glass Glass Tiles Glass Mosaics Glass and Stone
Live Customer Support (Mon-Fri)
Cement CementSelect from our many ready to ship patterns.
For custom patterns you can select from numerous designs and choose your own colors.
Custom colors require 6-8 week lead time.
Live Customer Support (Mon-Fri)
Live Customer Support (Mon-Fri)
